key choices all left to go back um is
terrible so I changed that to escape I'm
actually imported the I to key bindings
the only ones I care about are that and
of course pressing X to see you can see
the context here is a computed call you
didn't get 100 right now oh so that's
where everybody comes from I see what
it's delayed now all the people are
showing up yeah yeah we got lots of
people now hello are up to 92 people
yeah yeah so I figured this would make a
good stream you see this star code
pointer so let's look into the
decompiler code which i've already
brought up here for Ghidorah and let's
try to understand how this is working oh
I got a new Visual Studio code Java 12
support this is written in Java 11
so we're gonna try to figure out how
this works why is that stupid visual
studio color what's dirty Oh
are you doing laundry can you wash your
towels but don't wash them with anything
else except to the sheets cuz they're
dirty don't watch them when don't wash
them with my clothes cuz they're dirty
but towels are extremely dirty the
clothes are only a little dirty the
audio is only in the left ear is that
better
no but that's the deal but you might
have to fold them ones in the dryer put
them away
hi soon nos you're a subscriber welcome
so this is the steering firmware from
from a Honda Civic
hi haircut Jimmy you're a subscriber -
so what we're trying to fix today is
this so instead of saying pointer
finding table lookup um by the way just
to give you guys some context
hi there seven per am one ps4 eight so
these are the torque tables how do you
make an array how to do this let me can
array and get dress so I've never really
used Guidry before so I'm gonna be kind
of bad at this data create array who
enter the number of array elements maybe
we can tell from this oh that's just an
input to this function
why does xrefs take forever
[Music]
I've on 13 like one Fe can be the max
but it also comes from somewhere else
Aram to pass them through that from 10
okay this is extremely complex we're
just gonna look at the table and figure
out how big the table is ps4 8 is either
this pointer or this pointer and this is
passed in as 8 what's Ivar 7 well that
might not be a size thing see okay we
are gonna fix the bug but first we're
gonna find in table lookup oh I'm not
looking at the right thing okay
this is do torque curve look up here we
go these are the pointers I'm looking
for this is a pointer table look up this
is table look up that's what I want to
see okay cool do you audio in the left
ear seems like a problem let's see what
we can do about that
well it's probably just because this is
a stereo microphone audio sounds fine
okay I mean I guess we can put it here
but then it's harder for me to see the
screen yeah that's fine
it's not better now we can do real ask
more stuff you can hear me over here on
the left and you can hear me over here
and there right if I don't fall off my
chair now it is cuz I fixed that so if
we go back you can see this is this is
the actual function that looks up the
torque in the Honda Civic so I really
want to understand this code before oh
you're only hearing stuff in the left
all right well then you'll want to put
in the mic back over here because you
know this is too much for me all right
cool now please make the font a little
bigger I have I haven't the slightest
idea how to do
now we're gonna have to hear the washing
machine all stream does that make it
okay
[Music]
alright so D it's the same is it
supposed to be the same hotkey I try not
to rebind hotkeys when I use programs
because please quit KJ I have I to open
as well this is this is that same stuff
in in Ida but no Guidry is uh Ginger's
nice what was i pressing to do that d
for data oh it changes from B to D okay
it's B D usually means dis assemble and
disassemble that means see even those
C's already used from anything so k
create a right let's try something like
10 and see what we get Oh but I don't
like that it just hides them oh here we
go space ah beautiful
that chart article number of array
elements 85 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9
I believe there's 8 and we all know that
9 times 8 is know who knows what that is
it's a big number what's 9 times 8 72
good call oh wait did I just make an
array of arrays no oh wait good thing
this has undo that's something either
doesn't have right but I want to change
the array size of this huh do you see
what I did there I made an array of
arrays which was actually really cool
but that worked and that's almost what I
want create array what if I change it to
9 let's see what happens okay now it's
doing 9 by 10 so that's not actually
editing the existing array
kid just hard to you know choose word
ten gonna make some mafia is a good
choice bro I'm gonna create a right you
know what I can undo this and like just
go back here and it's actually nine by
and I want to make a eight array on top
of that and that's gonna do exactly what
I want
leave yeah
one of those is nine that's more than
that no it's only seven because these
are the data you see and these are the I
have to figure out how to edit this
there has to be a way fixed
audio by changing to Mono wait okay
let's check mine let's check my OBS and
see if it's actually messing up we can
we can fix this we have the technology
okay well I see that it's a little bit
unbalanced
[Music]
yeti stereo microphone yeti stereo
microphone yeti stereo mic wait no it's
still unbalanced even if I fold it over
here that's ten is that better well
something's like broken okay we're gonna
seriously invest to get the microphone
issue we're gonna open a bipartisan
committee to investigate the microphone
issue oh no but why is it just look you
can see it's not balanced how could that
even be a thing it's not like it's
actually stereo okay we're gonna try
something crazy when I unplug and replug
the microphone
you
okay it's still unbound
advanced audio properties balance oh
okay that's in the right I played with
the input modes okay that's not balanced
does that balance does that balance does
that balance no that's unbalanced but
this doesn't make sense right because
balance there is set to the middle we
can down mix to mono
well that fixes everything no but I
don't want to down mix tomorrow we want
to get to the bottom of the yeah I know
but no that's terrible I want stereo to
work because you people deserve stereo
sound no it's not fine look you can see
the top one going up more than the other
one um mono is king is the problem with
the mic no I know but if I go over here
it's still left and if I go over here
it's still left right so this is not the
problem
yeah we need stereo that's right no no
no guys we don't have time for this now
we're on a mission we're not gonna get
distracted by the stupid sound
we're just get it down next to mono know
like just Garage Band type settings for
this I know it works fine if I said at
the mono wait are you the guy who got
banned from PSN no but you're the guy
who got timeout it on my channel oh it
was terrible
okay now he's dared you on my team
now you can just come up it's no
no we're just gonna stick with we
clearly ain't good the audio gods but if
you have any idea there's no knob that
talks about balance or anything is just
gain and pattern it was funny it was
funny it's all it's over we're gonna
figure out how we raise whoa how'd I
just do that Dana settings
how do I on create an array without
using um Dale
now we actually want 9 times 7 which has
got to be something like almost 63 is
that about right sounds good um well I
wouldn't say the Honda software has a
bug I would say that the Honda software
doesn't have as much torque as people
might like so we're actually trying to
fix a bug in Deidre um I'll just point
out a word array
let me just make this an array as well I
wouldn't say it's a bug engager it could
very well be that I just don't know how
to use the software but um okay so this
is enter name is torque table ID X oh
look look how it changes to PTR that's
really nice
alright so now here we can see in dupe
torque curve lookup yeah this
there's got just be a setting for this
because these pointers oh it's probably
because they're in RAM oh this might be
really easy okay
so if it thinks that that pointer is
mutable it's not gonna want to change it
but if it thinks it's unmuted oh it'll
change it ah this might actually be easy
okay do you see what I'm saying like so
what this is doing this is an indirect
lookup right so it's it's a pc-relative
indirect lookup but I believe it has
this whole region marked as Ram so it
was mutable how does get your deal with
structs no I haven't really done structs
yet let's see if we can do this ah
where's the memory map
can figure I don't think it's that just
flight function crash let's see what
this looks like
well that's just like seg faulted oh no
here we go oh this is kind of nice
function graph browser in a way it's
better than Ida in a way it's worse than
I doubt okay oh when will I continue on
the checkmate exploit I remembered that
I remember it every reason that I hate
jailbreaking and stopped working on it
but I have student playing with video
which I really do like symbol table
symbol tree memory oh that's what I want
aha okay yeah so it thinks it's rwx
let's just get rid of the W oh my god
that fixed it oh dude you're so smart
look how it now says table lookup wow
that's the smartest thing I've ever seen
it didn't even make me reanalyze it
throws at the NSA you know when they say
like you ever seen those times at
Veronica you know the sign in Veronica
Mars this is your god government you
know what I'm talking about
I spelt god wrong it's it's it's on
Keith's Mars's wall in Veronica Mars no
no no I swear it's in Veronica Mars guys
there's a sign on the wall that has the
slogan of the US government and it says
this is your God and that's how I feel
right now wow that was just incredible
there there's the whole stream done in
20 minutes oh I'm so happy I thought of
that too all right
so now let's see what's actually going
on so this stuff's actually ramp um I'm
sure to automatically like figure out
where the RAM is sure we can create them
sound one memory mouth script manager
memory that edit add ha readwrite block
name real RAM initialize say
uninitialized
oh no it's dad - okay wait do I so what
do i do i reanalysis
otto analyze is that gonna turn those
two mmm Wow first I thought it was
lagging but then I realize I was just on
the wrong screen go
oh this is so good times nine Wow okay
the only thing missing that I would love
to see in Ghidorah um and I say is yes
all the NSA is a bunch of genius isn't
that this offers so good like look how
night this disassemble is better than
better than hex rays this is so good
torque
my wife
there we go it's pretty good context
data oh look now oh now it's doing these
as data of every analysis worked man
this is good okay the only thing that I
think gage is really missing is when you
click on something in Ida it lights them
all off so maybe we can figure out how
to do that
I don't know I did want to look at the
code in this stream um you know and I
don't like if I click this it would
light this one up too it's like really
good but I bet you that's like really
deep in their uses of byte data type
you know let's rename this cuz it's not
Iran program we'll name this one
okay you know which you know which
processor this is there's a data if
there's a data sheet somewhere it's one
of those renesis things on the civic
steering processor this is useless the
only place that might have it is
actually my code blue talk man never
mind
205 doesn't matter that much I think I
guess the RAM locations right if we find
weird ones don't match well now okay one
other things I don't like about this is
I actually don't think yeah cuz that's
not a that's not a ram address we want
to make it smaller maybe maybe I just
got the lame throw can i edit this
split a block ah and address now you can
delete this block she's probably no
references in here yeah so part of the
problem is yeah so these are not actual
references and this is messing up those
are just negative numbers and we don't
want to do that so dad yes oh no did
your craft but it seems okay
all of these address ffffff okay so yeah
that's what I wanted to avoid so I don't
know let's try the Auto analysis again
let's see if those go away
those are not addresses okay so you see
the analysis progress down here
no those shouldn't be there
whatever they're not affecting me right
now when they do affect me that's a good
later problem the table lookup fine and
table lookup oh this is so good
it's typing is pretty good as well like
this
and I understand that it's a bike
comparison but don't actually want that
to be at the SHA there's ways to fix
this in hideout properties D know all
these castes
we actually already did what the stream
came to do and all you had to do was set
the memory map to mark the memories not
writable it was actually absolutely
brilliant it's exactly the feature you'd
expect if anyone from the NSA is
watching and just saw that man you guys
really kill that okay I can show you a
little bit about what I'm doing and then
there's gonna be a short stream because
it was so easy I thought we'd have to go
into the code like I prepared I got to
get your code ready the D compiler is
written in C++
all right everybody can understand this
so if you look here Duke torque curve
lookup is being called with this Oh
times nine because it's all it's typed
wow that's so good okay you see how this
is times nine ah then the nine is okay
the nine is just a number of entries you
see one two three four five six seven
eight nine that's nine x torque row
choice and the reason it's times nine is
because it knows that this is a short
pointer so that's actually correct
pointer arithmetic in uh in C this thing
really written by geniuses these are the
tables that controls how much torque
your Honda Civic puts on the steering
wheel
we type variable
what is dot two to me
that looks better
judge arethe type it dude torque curves
look up okay this is the max thing where
is this number coming from torque input
clamp so you can see here this is being
clamped to what this is
this is a pointer to somewhere she I
don't know why it's when I press X on
that it says use of there's also a way
to like toggle P code display here
apparently this next different light
value just play bytes Wow just play
function call tree bookmarks was the
decompiler are there it is this D
compiler is so good no there's not a
debugger but yeah so this is
it's less than zero flip it around okay
and then it checks again if it's greater
than zero it flips it back around that's
the output value that's like a one clamp
output value why is it type does this
have
why don't I check the type of this
retype global oh it's a short pointer
all right cool so this is like like the
output of C this is kind of stupid too
cuz this +8 there and that's a real 8
which means it's a a zero so it's
different okay so that's just one of the
infuriating things about this code and
it's amazing like this is this is the
code that's running in the Honda Civic
steering firmware and they use global
variables all over the place you
shouldn't do this
and Trish thank you for gifting us up if
you love Ghidorah please subscribe to
the NSA please pay your taxes I you know
what honestly I feel better about paying
my taxes
another difference between Gidget and
Ida is Gidget decompiler works for every
processor so they have a processor like
intermediary language called slave which
D compiles this to P code let's see if
we can display P code
right what edit code layout not even
know that's her it really keeps drama
like it would be nice if I could click
on that and why when I press X does it
think it's use of short data type but
this just has to be some bug in the key
bindings cuz that's definitely not what
I want it's not what anybody would want
X has to mean two things
no find references to
yeah I want to reorder that can I do
that see the problem is the first thing
it's doing is the datatype manager
plugin she want to remove it from that I
can't
[Music]
click in the box clicking in the box
doesn't work I don't know ok where is
torque road choice coming from is this a
global variable yes it is when I used to
call it row selection I see so we can
actually I don't think we need a name
for that I think it'll automatically
become how do I reset the name to be the
pointer remove label ah perfect
oh that's so good you see how it
automatically calls it pointer and like
does exactly what you want because the
NSA is brilliant damn for che go thank
you for subscribing to my channel
so these nines okay so let's see number
char number of keys charge I'm gonna
change that type
find uses of charge no references to
address so let's see what this is
actually doing so remember keys is an
array of shorts valves and this is like
it's like a lookup at a table all right
so if we go back we can see the table
we're actually doing a lookup there and
they're like dude talk I've looked up
and the shows here table lookup so this
is the value that's being looked up
those are the indexes those are the
values and that's the number of indexes
or the number of keys all this is code
so easy to read now
auto-create structure not what I wanted
so this is like like main steering
function I have some better names for
these things in Ida I believe we can
look at what the same function looks
like in hideout
I call it that's due torque curve look
up the one before it doesn't have a name
and this is electronic torque table
lookup I don't know how good any of
these names are to r5 so what's the ABI
for this stuff
all these does table lookups so this is
like the final torque curve lookup let's
see what this function does we should be
able to trace it all the way through it
because I have the cam stuff I have the
canned stuff somewhere as well
I really give things terrible names so
it's e4e for is the steering command for
a Honda this is small can your CV for oh
it's so nice to be able to look at
things and see but again this is all
just use of global Global's everywhere I
don't know what that is
call this function can checksum
yeah that's right here look how easy it
is to read and see and confirm that
that's actually the can check some
function you want to see what bring up
the same code and open palette yeah look
at that that codes an open pilot I can
go find it confirm it's the same
so the Honda checksum would be in
self-drive car Honda Honda can that's
what the Honda that's what it looks like
in Python you can see what's basically
the same thing it's written more stupid
like with a lot of castes used well so
we know what the inputs to can check
some are this is address okay so the
problem here is that this is just a
wrong type I change that to unsigned
char star yeah looks so much better
call this address
all this when all this that not
beautiful look how good that looks
I mean you see it's it's the same as
this Python right here I don't know why
it feels like it has to do these 27
casts you wouldn't check some that's
right I don't know cameras TV for okay
so just check the check song
I really wish when I clicked it it would
light up maybe someone has a fix of
course it's useless
Oh try the middle mouse button Oh FK n
Dean killing it bro oh that's sick
middle click that middle click oh and I
say throw everything they my bros ok so
if the check sum 0 end it with 0 I
assume has to be a good thing yeah and
II four snaps so let's check the DBC
file and let's figure out what the e4
message is supposed to look like so we
can go in here you know what we should
change the title of this on the steering
firmware yeah yes something about that
yeah whatever because we solved the
problem so fast so here this is a sin
the civic touring so we can look at
steer steering controls here we go so
228 you go to 28 to hex it's gonna be e4
so steer torque is the first 16 bytes so
let's see if we can find the actual
canned data let's see how much I did in
Ida with respect to this Oh actually you
know exactly where the can date
the thing is pastor the check sum
function no alright so this is
actually an array yeah let's do this
carefully we're gonna call it can data
and then we're gonna make it an array
that's a long gate array wow that's a
lot of a right eight all right there's
panting can data here you know after
days use anywhere else this function you
know wow that's complex look in just
used anywhere else who's in a lot of
places
that's crazy complex you'll have a name
for it and verify can message with table
the same address okay well maybe old me
knew what I was doing all I care if I
can message with table 14 what it does
first change the type of this that and
the type is you cha
probably some table somewhere
I don't know maybe this actually does
the receive I mean this is this is looks
like it's actual I don't know this is a
game am i all right
okay if you receive successfully we're
gonna do the checksum on the data
what do things like this come from
Oh middle-click points P you've r2 where
does this come from GB are vitally
jubie's married
yo I'm asked you from the NSA NSA is bro
- he's married
yeah
one away I think we could say a bunch of
things about this all right I mean this
here
despite being part of these PU VARs is
clearly what do we call it steer torque
just call it a forced air tour that's
just a counter in Czech song
[Music]
we call this one candy for a status Walt
all right now let's see where this goes
not use of short datatype no oh I click
on it here so it's written to here it's
initialized here oh that's nice Oh
beautiful beautiful ah can an it efore
we can just rename this man this program
is so good ok so here's what we read it
in I don't know what that does but this
is the good one ok cool for steering so
if we really want to make safe
modifications to this firmware that
we're really sure what they do we want
to like understand what this whole
parsing path looks like so here it's
multiplying it I believe that's the
square root of 3 checking some bounds
this doesn't look right
how'd it go this all maybe the returned
doesn't actually matter
okay so this reads the steering torgan
it looks like it sets it into here with
all this process just call it e 4r steer
or d DB for doing
this is some processing function it
looks like it runs every once in a while
let's go here right click there go there
I do wish xrefs was faster how come
X isn't working
references references I understand why I
couldn't press X and do that ok
that's what right set where's it read
per am what does it think that's a
parameter also kappa ramm to a function
I see
oh there we go that one Noah back where
we were okay perfect
I don't know what that's for
but here is like here's the function we
were in before and we see it just gets
passed in there perfect unfortunately it
does get fed up here we go so this is
just deer torque for if it's less than
zero
it adds three shifts it over man this is
complex do you references it as an
integer which I guess it is an integer
because it was multiplied by stuff it's
less than zero it adds three it shifts
it over to and makes it a short then it
does some other complicated and
then it saves it over here so let's call
this you for capacitor
it's only ready to great not useful um
so it's also passed in here to
electronic torque table lookup these
other values are passed in here there's
also a speed table this might be the
speed table choice boy about 12 and how
do I make that not hex no I can't
yeah so these are these are tables very
similar to this is twelve tables
oh no it's just oh it's twelve cuz it
wasn't ah I get it I get it I get it
alright um still times nine so it's
probably the same 72 as before it's
creating a variety of 72 makes sense
yeah I think 72 makes sense no it's
actually one less so if it's one last 72
minus 9 is 63 there we go
yeah because you see this reference is
here so create array yo I trust be
honest a man I'm an American
they're not like the you know at the
young army the FBI bus Americans man the
NSA like no no I was little Wayne would
say they spawned all of our I think
this is speed
so this is the speed clamp I'm not sure
what it does with this or read it here
of course we only write to it
well this one gets red I hate they use
global variables don't do it
torque speed clamp copy let's figure out
why this is red no no no no this be
table lookups torque speed clamp copy
here go look read ah you know electronic
torque table lookup
so what's called here here we go and now
we're getting somewhere
cuz this thing passed in here well I
don't know about that
that can't be the only use of around to
is that no you only use a program to is
that plus six so this e for steer torque
isn't actually used they're just that a
six to make see var1 I love that I found
this click though throw it to click you
know what you're doing um torque speed
clamp copy where is this used multiplied
yeah hmm that's not what I expected
tickets a scaling factor or something
Global variables everywhere it's also
extremely dangerous and hard to analyze
multiplied now let's try going at it
from the other way and seeing where the
input to this comes up because this is
the input this is torque input we know
that where we have here clamp you put
value here we go why doesn't it resolve
this I don't know what that +8 supposed
to be times are four so why isn't it
resolve that to this which it should be
she's annoying that is hard to resolve
because it is 8 here I don't know why it
didn't resolve this
it's too far away
one day I want to take a shirtless
picture on Instagram yeah what why does
this say equals question question
question question this resolves fine oh
wait I think this is right so calls this
and then this is a pointer oh I should
check the type of this that's a little
annoyed
no it's int it's not I don't know it's
just doing 2d references is this a
pointer or not let's figure out what
rights do it yes its pointer
it's a pointer that we don't know the
stuff for
well it's okay that it's a pointer
let's call it pointer torque stuff
this is all an electronic torque table
okay why don't they show me what
function it's in function name
here we go why was that not default
that's so good alright so yeah all of
this is an electronic torque table look
I could good
[Music]
she's in speed clamp copy
is this the same +8 I don't know
you see we see this plus 8y is this an
undefined ways the one with 8 even here
800 are 10 that's what's being said
there okay type undefined to type int
it's being cast on define to some reason
it can't tell what type is what type is
that when we look it up and so this is
electronic torque table lookup and dupe
torque curve lookup it's a short so we
can just re-type this as a short
yeah and this is so this is the torque
yeah and this can like add things or
subtract things in the tour think this
comes in from there which comes in from
there which is actually per am one
what is per am one I've r75 are seven
comes from here which is this what is
this not uses of short datatype no not
what i want this we write it here comes
from this function it comes from here
okay this is a rabbit hole
who's this function
not too much stuff
so my Bitcoin address guru uh tower comm
towel room let's say yeah that's good
because active routes are so last summer
y'all let's listen to that
open Spotify there we go
but is that really where I linked to
from that
you
this is kind of calming I related
what this is a Honda Civics can't steer
below 12 miles an hour
so if you just change this 28 to a zero
it fixes that input speed
I think it's kph times 2
[Music]
you
it's also scary if I can be negative
sometimes
you
raise
just be a
well it's greater than one it's the main
thing I don't understand is this shift
shift right one it wouldn't make sense
but
it's just a left there when it does the
key lookup if Val is less than save the
output why is it having number of keys
add one if it's less than zero that's
when you return
finding table lookup is actually
supposed to return
table
just just the index it was as soon as
this one extra one at the admin to sell
I'm actually gonna be a howl of you at
the oak so it just no no it should be an
index oh that's correct
it's the number of keys
oh it's binary search oh I get it
oh that's clever oh look at sad see what
it's doing
yeah okay so if it's less than yeah if
it's less than it closes that off so it
does binary search yeah very cool cool
all right
the only way that we're really gonna
answer that question is if if the only
way we're really going to answer the
question is if we just get that to
compile quickly and say so let's just do
that
table
and you even write tests based on this
decompiled code
let's copy and paste the tables do do
and put to our clam that's not bad it's
cold
no babies
you torque curve look up that's it you
have to read me the X all right it's a
table lookup I pass in the value now
when we look up X 100
[Music]
all right so now we can answer the
coffee at 1680
guess we got lucky oh I checked it right
at the top there if keys is less than
Val local if a local is listing cuter
Bret oh so just even do that I was
beautiful good so my people are out this
code
beautiful alright cool guys that's gonna
be a hard one to follow
maybe wall will follow it later in the
archive is a question time and you won't
have any quick questions before we go so
for reference what we did today is we
just confirmed we found that it wasn't
actually a bug in deidre we just had to
not ask some questions about
keyboards wasn't actually a bug we just
have to set it to not writable and we
figured out that it's safe to run off
the table and I'm a little concerned
about the speed thing now because it
seems like it's a multiply why are we
doing this what wouldn't it be nice if
your Honda instead of turning like this
could turn like this you know what's the
theory behind square root of three being
a right shift of n so I believe that we
can bring this up into Python gdb for
let's do D D D D for this RL wrapped so
if we take some number like 1000 and we
multiply it by D D D 4 and then we write
shift it 0 F we get like this right and
then if we do in for math math dot
squared 3 we get basically the same
thing
why is it multiplied by the square root
of three well so it's a torque it
probably has to do with the fact that
it's like a three-phase motor or
something I couldn't tell you exactly I
don't really know what the units are
where's the razor blade it's for sale I
want to buy it do you have a gmail if
you want to buy it I'll sell to you yeah
like name a fair price if you want it
it's yours yeah it's a multiply and then
a chef so this is a way to do a divide
without actually doing it of anything in
float so it's like a new division I'm
using a 13-inch MacBook but you know
come on guys no no no answer is about no
no when I have an unanswered question
about all projects either we are gonna
come back to twitch twitch
will happen again but I work today side
to work today there's more cool bits I
don't know why I just copy down the hill
Nicole could I make a course on
something what's twitch cop check my
github this was just a little side
project this was what I did today and we
uncovered something concerning which
some things a multiply that I don't
think was a multiply
1 million followers I'm climbing much
Nisan did you see GCC's unreadable
garbage they're asking how I got into
college
alright since I think it's too late for
any of this to have concept now now
there's other people involved but you
know let's just say if someone ever told
you to be yourself when you're going to
college that's bad advice if you care
about going to college I think the
system is after 2014 I think the college
the university system is beyond their
cult man as it's just a cult would I
still be successful who said I'm
successful bro let's cuz I'm rich yeah
yeah it turns out you don't need college
for any of that yeah you do something to
protect your eyes from what
locking the domestic clock on bootloader
should we break it mobile to get me
I do need 1 million followers that's
right
[Music]
some 3050 people I will pay up him right
back
now you're gonna work ass girl work work
time no room tiller
oh you follow me on LinkedIn bro
LinkedIn is the biggest joke of a social
network ever if you're expecting
anything from LinkedIn you know how long
I've had a post on my LinkedIn that I
want a date and like let's just say of
all the dating platforms LinkedIn is the
lowest quality do you really want like
career climbing women that's what you
get on LinkedIn do you really want
career climbing men do you really want
career climbing people and the answer is
no so don't look on LinkedIn
your subscriber so I won't ban you for
that ps4 chat but this is how much I
care about the ps4 see this that's too
much that's how much I care
finish it what you're gonna get a
diploma you gonna wake up you're gonna
feel good about yourself because you got
a diploma on the wall I never had no
AT&T yeah
you subbed thank you Thank You Johnny
Carl I appreciate it
all but job posts oh so you can get
validation from some guy there's plenty
of jobs that will hire you without a
college education
I have no college education I've worked
Google I've worked at Facebook I've
worked at SpaceX to be fair I was an
intern at a contractor for Google I was
full-time at Facebook that got by him
and I was Internet SpaceX but look if
you want full-time jobs you can get him
you just got to prove yourself
what I fail I didn't go to college so I
can't be Amazon intern that's too bad
come on mr. Bezos hey I'll make you a
deal
next summer Jeff Bezos if you offer me
an internship
I'll come your turn on Amazon Oh what
can one have you want but it's got to be
from Jeff Bezos that's right now we
gotta get tea love to get a tea with
Jeff Bezos so I think that'd be cool I'm
going to do github roasting again no no
we did that we did that or did it last
time
we're gonna make a thing out of it
should it be fill time so we watch some
dr. Phil and make fun of it pretty nice
so it's pretty nice implementation it's
binary search and I can't believe it he
compiled so nicely it's beautiful
how did jump tables relate to steering
wheel solid jump table it's like just a
lookup
I was jumped Amberleigh at the steering
wheel so this is the code that runs on
the steering controller the Honda
watch my code blue talk if you want to
figure out how to get it
[Music]
have you looked into rust yeah I know a
little bit of rust I was an intern at
SpaceX I was an intern pretty cool very
cool you know
I wish there would have been something
if I could if I felt like I could
actually contribute something to the
Mars effort like beyond being like you
know mid tier engineer I would why does
the car limit the steering in the first
place of time for safety um like for
example the Toyotas I think don't limit
the steering enough the Honda's limited
a bit too much you know all right I
gotta go it's probably lunch time at
work I'm gonna go eat lunch at work am I
not a 10x engineer when I'm motivated I
don't know I like an established project
probably not to get things started into
design things well they're probably my
favorite programming language that's
been going on Twitter